<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<book title="Mekanism HandyGuide" cover="mekanism:item/alloy_infused" fontSize="1.0">
    <include ref="gbook:xml/standard.xml"/>

    <chapter>
        <section>
            <!--
            'p' tags draw text, and increment the vertical offset.
            They do NOT behave exactly like in html.
            The space attribute changes the default spacing added after the paragraph.
            -->
            <p color="#606060" space="8">This book is a work in progress.</p>


            <section-break/>

            <!--
            'space' tags increment the vertical offset without drawing text.
            The 'height' attribute specifies how much.
            The % refers to a % of the section's height, while integer values refer to pixels.
            -->
            <space height="33%"/>
            <p space="8" align="center" scale="2">Mekanism</p>
            <p align="center">Here at Mekanism, Inc. we pride ourselves on our user-friendly creations, but sometimes a
                little nudge in the right direction is needed. Enter: the Mekanism HandyGuide - your handy dandy guide
                to the world of Mekanism.
            </p>
        </section>
        <section>
            <page_title>
                <title>Index</title>
            </page_title>
            <p>Introduction</p>
            <link indent="8" ref="intro">Introduction</link>
            <link indent="8" ref="intro:features">Main Features</link>

            <link ref="functional_blocks">Functional Blocks</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:antiprotonic_nucleosynthesizer" indent="8">Antiprotonic Nucleosynthesizer</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:bins" indent="8">Bins</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:chargepad" indent="8">Chargepad</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:chemical_crystallizer" indent="8">Chemical Crystallizer</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:chemical_dissolution_chamber" indent="8">Chemical Dissolution Chamber</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:chemical_infuser" indent="8">Chemical Infuser</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:chemical_injection_chamber" indent="8">Chemical Injection Chamber</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:chemical_oxidizer" indent="8">Chemical Oxidizer</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:chemical_tank" indent="8">Chemical Tanks</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:chemical_washer" indent="8">Chemical Washer</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:combiner" indent="8">Combiner</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:crusher" indent="8">Crusher</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:digital_miner" indent="8">Digital Miner</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:dimensional_stabilizer" indent="8">Dimensional Stabilizer</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:electric_pump" indent="8">Electric Pump</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:electrolytic_separator" indent="8">Electrolytic Separator</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:energized_smelter" indent="8">Energized Smelter</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:energy_cube" indent="8">Energy Cube</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:enrichment_chamber" indent="8">Enrichment Chamber</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:factories" indent="8">Factories</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:fluidic_plenisher" indent="8">Fluidic Plenisher</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:fluid_tank" indent="8">Fluid Tanks</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:formulaic_assemblicator" indent="8">Formulaic Assemblicator</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:fuelwood_heater" indent="8">Fuelwood Heater</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:isotopic_centrifuge" indent="8">Isotopic Centrifuge</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:logistical_sorter" indent="8">Logistical Sorter</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:metallurgic_infuser" indent="8">Metallurgic Infuser</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:modification_station" indent="8">Modification Station</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:nutritional_liquifier" indent="8">Nutritional Liquifier</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:oredictionificator" indent="8">Oredictionificator</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:osmium_compressor" indent="8">Osmium Compressor</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:painting_machine" indent="8">Painting Machine</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:personal_barrel" indent="8">Personal Barrel</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:personal_chest" indent="8">Personal Chest</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:pigment_extractor" indent="8">Pigment Extractor</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:pigment_mixer" indent="8">Pigment Mixer</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:precision_sawmill" indent="8">Precision Sawmill</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:pressurized_reaction_chamber" indent="8">Pressurized Reaction Chamber</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:purification_chamber" indent="8">Purification Chamber</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:resistive_heater" indent="8">Resistive Heater</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:robit" indent="8">Robit</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:rotary_condensentrator" indent="8">Rotary Condensentrator</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:seismic_vibrator" indent="8">Seismic Vibrator</link>
            <link ref="functional_blocks:solar_neutron_activator" indent="8">Solar Neutron Activator</link>

            <link ref="gear">Gear</link>

            <link ref="items">Items</link>

            <!--<link ref="API">1. Adding new Books</link>
            <link indent="8" ref="API:respack">1.1. Via Resource Packs</link>
            <link indent="8" ref="API:configuration">1.2. Via Config Folder</link>
            <link ref="XML">2. Structure of the book</link>
            <link indent="8" ref="XML:pages">2.1. Chapters and Pages</link>
            <link indent="8" ref="XML:text">2.2. Paragraphs and titles</link>
            <link indent="8" ref="XML:images">2.3. Images and Links</link>
            <link indent="8" ref="XML:stacks">2.4. Item Stacks</link>
            <link ref="templates">3. Templates (WIP)</link>
            <link indent="8" ref="templates:recipes">3.1. Recipes (WIP)</link>-->
        </section>
    </chapter>
    <chapter id="intro">
        <section>
            <page_title>
                <title>Introduction</title>
            </page_title>
            <p space="8">Mekanism is an independent tech mod that brings many different machinery types to Minecraft,
                solving
                problems nobody knew they had. The mod doesn't have any main goals, and you'll notice this when you see
                the seemingly random content Mekanism contains (from jetpacks to balloons). However, there is a somewhat
                linear progression system that is both easy to follow and increases in complexity as the player becomes
                more accustomed to the mod, making sure that the player will have an easy time getting into the mod
                without ever getting bored with it.
            </p>
            <p space="8">By the time anybody has finished a mod pack using Mekanism, if they
                play a pack without it in the future, the first thought would be "Man, I wish I had Mekanism!". This
                seemingly simple mod has so much to offer to anybody willing to play, with minimal (but necessary grind)
                and ample rewards for the player's efforts.
            </p>
            <p space="8">Mekanism uses a tier-based system when organizing several of its core features (for instance:
                <link ref="functional_blocks:energy_cube">Energy Cubes</link> and <link ref="functional_blocks:factories">Factories</link>).
            </p>
            <p space="8">There are four tiers: basic (green), advanced (red), elite (cyan), and ultimate
                (purple), with each tier ordered respectively in increasing order in terms of energy consumption and
                processing slots.
            </p>
            <p space="8">Mekanism does not directly increase processing speed every tier, instead it adds extra
                processing slots which all process the inputted materials at the same time. Basic has 3 slots, advanced
                has 5 slots, elite has 7 slots, and ultimate has 9 slots.
            </p>
            <p space="8">By the time the player has gotten used to using Mekanism, they will have unlimited sand and
                gravel just from a cobblestone generator, will have a simplistic sorting systems for all of their items,
                will be obtaining five ingots for each ore they mine, and will be boasting their powerful, heavily
                equipped, and very protective Mekasuit alongside with their even more powerful Mekatool, which combines
                the power of Vein miners, Tree Fellers, Axes, Swords, Pickaxes, Shovels, and Hoes.
            </p>
        </section>
        <section id="features">
            <page_title>
                <title>Main Features</title>
            </page_title>
            <p space="4" bold="true">Power Compatibility</p>
            <p space="8">Unless disabled in the configuration, Mekanism accepts power in and can convert to/from a number of energy formats: Mekanism Joules, Forge Energy, IC2 Energy Units (EU), and Flux Networks. NB: IC2 Classic is not actively supported.</p>

            <p space="4" bold="true">Ore Processing</p>
            <p space="8">Mekanism features an extremely advanced, extensive ore processing system. From simple machines used to process ores into ingots electronically, to complex chemical-based ore injection used to gain four ingots for every ore mined, Mekanism covers basic smelting, as well as 2x, 3x, and 4x duplication.</p>
            <p space="8">All machines have configurable input and eject sides, allowing you to have complete control over how you want to manage your machinery.</p>

            <p space="4" bold="true">Factories</p>
            <p space="8">Mekanism introduces the concept of "<link ref="functional_blocks:factories">factories</link>", which are multi-operation machines that can process multiple stacks of ores simultaneously. In a single machine, you can be smelting several stacks of ore into ingots, enriching several stacks of ores into dusts, or crushing several stacks of cobblestone into gravel.</p>

            <p space="4" bold="true">Ores</p>
            <p space="8">Mekanism is founded on the resource Osmium which generates pretty commonly at any Y level below 60. Osmium can be used to create tools and armor, but it is primarily used in the making of machinery.</p>
            <p space="8">Tin, Copper, Gold &amp; Bronze are also used in crafting recipes.</p>

            <p space="4" bold="true">Armor and Tools</p>
            <p space="8">Mekanism brings five new sets of armor and tools to the table, as well as the ever-famed Paxel (an all-in-one tool).</p>

            <p space="8">However, as Mekanism is a "tech mod," it has to have some cool techy gadgets. The Atomic Disassembler is an expensive, electronic multi-tool that can be set to mine at different speeds. Can't forget the Jetpack and Scuba Mask/Tank combination.</p>

            <p space="4" bold="true">Robit</p>
            <p space="8">The Robit is a cute little electronic robot that will follow you around and collect item drops for you. He also serves as a portable furnace, workbench, anvil, chest, and spirit lifter.</p>

            <p space="4" bold="true">Mining</p>
            <p space="8">Mekanism introduces the "Digital Miner" - an automated mining machine that can sort through terrain and pick out the resources you specify. It uses a filter-based system, and will then go through the range you specify and mine the blocks it needs to.</p>

            <p space="4" bold="true">Dynamic Tanks</p>
            <p space="8">These are multiblock tanks that can be shaped as any rectangular prism (capping at 18x18x18).</p>

            <p space="4" bold="true">Transmitters (AKA pipes)</p>
            <p space="8">Mekanism features multiple ways of transmitting items, fluids, gasses, heat and energy from once place to another, using devices we call "transmitters."</p>

            <p space="4" bold="true">Quantum IO (QIO)</p>
            <p space="8">QIO is a way of storing large amounts of items that can be stored, searched, and accessed remotely in late game.</p>
        </section>
    </chapter>
    <chapter id="functional_blocks">
        <section id="antiprotonic_nucleosynthesizer">
            <page_title><title>Antiprotonic Nucleosynthesizer</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:antiprotonic_nucleosynthesizer"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">A machine which uses bits of antimatter and mass amounts of energy to atomically transmute various resources.</p>
            <!-- TODO elaborate! -->
        </section>
        <section id="chargepad">
            <page_title><title>Chargepad</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:chargepad"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">The Chargepad is a wireless electric charging station. Any rechargeable items you have in your inventory will be charged while standing on it.</p>
            <p space="8">It also functions as the deployment and teleportation point for your <link ref="functional_blocks:robit">Robit</link>.</p>
            <p space="8">The Chargepad requires a source of power to function, which can only be supplied through the bottom of the pad via any compatible energy cable.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="bins">
            <page_title><title>Bins</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:basic_bin"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <p space="8" align="center">
                <stack item="mekanism:basic_bin"/>
                <stack item="mekanism:advanced_bin"/>
                <stack item="mekanism:elite_bin"/>
                <stack item="mekanism:ultimate_bin"/>
            </p>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">Bins are storage blocks that can store a large quantity of a single item; the amount of which depends on its tier. It will retain its inventory when broken with a pickaxe or removed using a Configurator (or other wrench).</p>
            <p space="8">Bins have a single storage slot that ignores normal item stacking limits, allowing a large amount of a single type of item to be stored in them.</p>
            <p space="8">However, bins do not bypass the requirement for every item in the stack to share the same NBT data. As a result, renamed, enchanted, or damaged items can not be stacked in the bin; nor can most other items which don't stack in your inventory.</p>
            <title>Portable Inventory</title>
            <p space="8">As bins retain their inventory when picked up, they can be used as portable item storage, similar to how Shulker Boxes act in vanilla. Unlike Shulker Boxes, bins permit items to be both inserted and extracted without needing to place it down in the world.</p>
            <p space="8">To insert items, the bin can be placed into a crafting grid along with the items the player desires to add, and then removing the bin from the output slot, as long as the items to be inserted are the same as what is already in the bin. To extract items, the bin can be placed in a crafting grid with no other items; from there items can be extracted one stack at a time from the output slot.</p>
            <title>Comparator Interaction</title>
            <p space="8">The amount of items inside a bin can be measured using a redstone comparator. The signal strength is based on a percentage of the total capacity used, with 15 being completely full.</p>
            <p space="8">Note that in the case of the Creative Bin, either 0 or 15 will be outputted depending on whether there is an item in the bin, as the Creative Bin contains an infinite amount of the given item.</p>
            <title>Automation</title>
            <p space="8">Items can be inserted and extracted from any side of the Bin using Hoppers, Logistical Transporters, or any item pipe from another mod.</p>
            <p space="8">By sneak right-clicking a bin with a Configurator set to any Configurate mode, auto-output can be toggled. When enabled, items will automatically be ejected one stack at a time into any inventory or Logistical Transporter on the bottom of the bin, assuming that the destination can accept the item. It will not dump items as entities into the world in the event that the block below is not a suitable inventory. A bin will glow when auto-output is enabled.</p>
            <title>Upgrading Tier</title>
            <p space="8">It is possible to upgrade a bin by using it in place of an empty bin in the crafting recipe for the next tier of bin. This will not result in the loss of the contents of the bin used in the upgrade.</p>
            <p space="8">Similar to machines, bins can also be upgraded through the use of tier installers. By holding the installer in the main hand and sneak right-clicking the bin, the current bin will be replaced with the next tier of bin while keeping its current inventory. Note that tiers can not be skipped.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="chemical_crystallizer">
            <page_title><title>Chemical Crystallizer</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:chemical_crystallizer"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">The Chemical Crystallizer turns Clean Slurry into Crystals, Lithium into Lithium Dust and Antimatter into Antimatter Pellet.</p>
            <p space="8">This is one of the select many machines in Mekanism to have dedicated, unchangeable sides, for input and output, with the exception of Item's config sides.</p>
            <p space="8">The input is gas/chemical (uses Pressurized Tube) and the output is items</p>
        </section>
        <section id="chemical_dissolution_chamber">
            <page_title><title>Chemical Dissolution Chamber</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:chemical_dissolution_chamber"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">The Chemical Dissolution Chamber turns raw ores into slurry using Sulfuric Acid. This is part of the 5x ore multiplication pipeline.</p>
            <p space="8">This slurry then needs washing in the <link ref="functional_blocks:chemical_washer">Chemical Washer</link>.</p>
            <p space="8">Note that unlike most Mekanism machines this one has fixed "in" and "out" sides for the mineral flow. "Out" is on the right (larger connector), gas "in" the left (smaller connector) and minerals "in" the top. It can of course be rotated with the Configurator.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="chemical_infuser">
            <page_title><title>Chemical Infuser</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:chemical_infuser"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">The Chemical Infuser combines or reacts two gases to create another gas.</p>
            <p space="8">The gas gauges on the left and right side of its GUI are the input tanks, and correspond to correspond with the left and right sides of the machine.</p>
            <p space="8">The gauge in the middle is for the resulting gas, which likewise is output through the front of the machine.</p>
            <p space="8">These recipes do not require the gas to be in a certain tank (i.e. left/right tank doesn't matter).</p>
            <p space="8">Should you get the wrong gas into either of the tanks, you can use the Gauge Dropper to empty or transfer it.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="chemical_injection_chamber">
            <page_title><title>Chemical Injection Chamber</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:chemical_injection_chamber"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8" align="center">
                <stack item="mekanism:basic_injecting_factory"/>
                <stack item="mekanism:advanced_injecting_factory"/>
                <stack item="mekanism:elite_injecting_factory"/>
                <stack item="mekanism:ultimate_injecting_factory"/>
            </p>
            <p space="8">The Chemical Injection Chamber uses Hydrogen Chloride gas to turn ores into 4 Shards.</p>
            <p space="8">It is the start of x4 ore processing and requires a steady supply of Hydrogen Chloride.</p>
            <p space="8">It can also turn Water Vapor and Dirt into Clay.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="chemical_oxidizer">
            <page_title><title>Chemical Oxidizer</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:chemical_oxidizer"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">The Chemical Oxidizer is used for making gases from materials.</p>
            <p space="8">Its left side accepts incoming materials, while it's right side dispenses the gas created from those materials.</p>
            <p space="8">This machine is part of the 5x ore multiplication pipeline.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="chemical_tank">
            <page_title><title>Chemical Tanks</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:basic_chemical_tank"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8" align="center">
                <stack item="mekanism:basic_chemical_tank"/>
                <stack item="mekanism:advanced_chemical_tank"/>
                <stack item="mekanism:elite_chemical_tank"/>
                <stack item="mekanism:ultimate_chemical_tank"/>
            </p>
            <p space="8">Chemical Tanks (previously Gas Tanks) are used to store Gases, Slurries, Pigments, and Infusion elements. They can be placed as a block and can interact with Pressurized Tubes.</p>
            <p space="8">They come in the four tiers, each tier being double the capacity and output rate of its predecessor.</p>
            <title>Configurations</title>
            <p space="8">By default, the chemical tank will be set input on all sides, barring the front which will be set to output, (all substances). Auto eject will also be On by default, so substances will be inserted into connected Pressurized tubes on the output side(s).</p>
            <title>Dumping</title>
            <p space="4">Chemical tanks have a dump feature, which can be toggled via the button in the GUI</p>
            <p space="4">Idle</p>
            <p space="8">The chemical tank will not dump anything.</p>
            <p space="4">Dump Excess</p>
            <p space="8">The chemical tank will limit its storage to only 99.5% of its full capacity while voiding any excess, causing the tank to never be full.</p>
            <p space="4">Dump</p>
            <p space="8">The chemical tank will continuously dump (void) its entire inventory, attempting to leave none left. Dumping is not instantaneous.</p>
            <title>Item Inventory</title>
            <p space="8">The Chemical Tank, when placed in the world, has two slots in its inventory.</p>
            <p space="8">The slot with a blue negative sign is the input slot. If you place something that contains a chemical (e.g. a chemical tank containing Oxygen) into this slot, the chemical tank will drain the item of its content as much as possible.</p>
            <p space="8">The slot with a red positive sign is the output slot. If you place something that can store a chemical (e.g. a chemical tank) into this slot, the chemical tank will fill the item as much as possible.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="chemical_washer">
            <page_title><title>Chemical Washer</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:chemical_washer"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">The Chemical Washer turns Slurry into Clean Slurry using Water.</p>
            <p space="8">The clean slurry then needs to be further refined by pumping it into a Chemical Crystallizer.</p>
            <p space="8">Note that unlike most Mekanism machines this one has fixed "in" and "out" sides for the mineral flow. "In" will be on the left when first placed and "out" is on the right.</p>
            <p space="8">Water is piped in through the top of the machine.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="combiner">
            <page_title><title>Combiner</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:combiner"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8" align="center">
                <stack item="mekanism:basic_combining_factory"/>
                <stack item="mekanism:advanced_combining_factory"/>
                <stack item="mekanism:elite_combining_factory"/>
                <stack item="mekanism:ultimate_combining_factory"/>
            </p>
            <p space="8">The Combiner allows the player to create an ore block from cobblestone and dust/gems.</p>
            <p space="8">Recipes are intended to require more input than would be gained from mining a block, it is not an ore multiplication tool</p>
        </section>
        <section id="crusher">
            <page_title><title>Crusher</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:crusher"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8" align="center">
                <stack item="mekanism:basic_crushing_factory"/>
                <stack item="mekanism:advanced_crushing_factory"/>
                <stack item="mekanism:elite_crushing_factory"/>
                <stack item="mekanism:ultimate_crushing_factory"/>
            </p>
            <p space="8">A machine used to crush ingots into their dust counterparts, stones into finer stones, etc.</p>
            <p space="8">Note that it does <span bold="true">not</span> perform Ore to Dust conversion, which is the job of the <link ref="functional_blocks:enrichment_chamber">Enrichment Chamber</link>.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="digital_miner">
            <page_title><title>Digital Miner</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:digital_miner"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">A highly-advanced, filter-based, auto-miner that can mine just about whatever block you tell it to.</p>
            <title>Usage</title>
            <p space="8">To begin, the Digital Miner needs a source of power. It can be powered through its energy slot (green border in the GUI) or by one of its three energy ports (indicated by a green square), which are situated on the sides and bottom.</p>
            <p space="8">In the main interface, click on the Config button to specify the area and filters for it to use. If you do not wish to leave empty spaces where ore blocks used to be, fill the block replacement slot with any block, turn on the requirement in the filters, and supply the necessary blocks in the machine's inventory.</p>
            <p space="8">Once powered and your filters made, hit the Start button back in the main interface to start mining. You will need to stop it and press the Reset button to change the configuration.</p>
            <p space="8">The Digital Miner has two item ports (indicated by a yellowish-tan square) - the one on the back, where output items go (auto-eject or pulled) and the one on the top to insert replacement blocks. Replacement items can be pulled from an inventory attached to the top port when Auto-Pull is turned on.</p>
            <p space="8">To speed up the miner, use speed upgrades. To increase the energy capacity and efficiency of the miner, install energy upgrades. Up to 8 can be used for a 10x effect for both upgrades.</p>
            <p space="8">Please note that if the Miner is unable to mine blocks, there may be a protection mod in place which does not allow the Miner to function (i.e. Chunk Protection). The miner will make best efforts to use the owner's permissions but compatibility cannot be guaranteed.</p>
            <title>Modes/Toggles</title>
            <p space="4" bold="true">Inverse Mode</p>
            <p space="8">Inverse mode mines everything that is not in the filter list. When Inverse is turned on, the replacement block and required replacement options are configured below the Inverse toggle.</p>
            <p space="4" bold="true">Silk Touch Mode</p>
            <p space="8">Emulates the silk touch enchantment. This mode requires 6x the usual amount of energy.</p>
            <p space="4" bold="true">Auto-Eject</p>
            <p space="8">When a block is mined, the block will automatically be sent to a connected Logistical Transporter or Inventory connected to the rear item port. If ejection is not possible, the item will remain in the Miner's inventory and be pushed out when possible. Note that space in the Miner's Inventory is always required to mine.</p>
            <p space="4" bold="true">Auto-Pull</p>
            <p space="8">Combined with Block Replacement mode, the Auto-Pull function will attempt to pull replacement blocks from an Inventory connected to the top item port. Without this, replacement blocks must be present in the Miner's inventory (which must also have room for mined blocks).</p>
            <p space="4" bold="true">Block Replacement</p>
            <p space="8">When a block is mined, you can choose to leave another block in its it by specifying a block in the filter. The replacement can be required (the miner will stop until it can replace the block), or optional (miner will continue without replacement). Using Auto-Pull mode with this feature is highly recommended.</p>
            <title>Other Config</title>
            <p space="8">Remember to click the tick button (or the return key) after entering a number for these settings.</p>
            <p space="4" bold="true">Radi (Radius)</p>
            <p space="8">Sets the radius of the area to mine, i.e. this distance in each horizontal direction around the miner.</p>
            <p space="4" bold="true">Min &amp; Max</p>
            <p space="8">Sets the minimum and maximum Y-level for the mining area</p>
            <title>Filter Types</title>
            <p space="4" bold="true">ItemStack (Item)</p>
            <p space="8">Searches for this specific Block.</p>
            <p space="4" bold="true">Tag</p>
            <p space="8">Uses the tag system to search for Blocks in a group. You can use a Dictionary to find these.</p>
            <p space="8">Type a name and click the green tick to check your entry.</p>
            <p space="4">Some examples</p>
            <p space="8"><span italics="true">forge:ores</span> - All ores</p>
            <p space="8"><span italics="true">forge:ores/iron</span> - All Iron ore variants</p>
            <p space="8"><span italics="true">forge:sand</span> - Sand</p>
            <p space="8"><span italics="true">minecraft:logs</span> - Wood Logs</p>
            <p space="4" bold="true">Mod ID</p>
            <p space="8">Searches for any block from a specific mod. Mod IDs are all lowercase and can often be found online on wikis.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="dimensional_stabilizer">
            <page_title><title>Dimensional Stabilizer</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:dimensional_stabilizer"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">A machine that prevents areas of the world from disappearing when not observed (a chunkloader).</p>
            <p space="8">In exchange for power, keeps a configured area loaded when a player is not around (max 5x5 chunks).</p>
            <p space="8">In the GUI, the area can be configured. Note that it is relative to North, but you can use the Show Visuals button to check in-world.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="electric_pump">
            <page_title><title>Electric Pump</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:electric_pump"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">A powered pump to extract fluids from the world. It will extract fluid from source blocks connected to the block directly under it (and removed them).</p>
            <p space="8">Water blocks will not be removed by default.</p>
            <p space="8">When a Filter Upgrade is installed, the pump will produce Heavy Water from Water.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="electrolytic_separator">
            <page_title><title>Electrolytic Separator</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:electrolytic_separator"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">The Electrolytic Separator performs electrolysis on fluids to create some very useful gases from some rather ordinary fluids.</p>
            <p space="8">The Electrolytic Separator requires a constant supply of power and must have a source of a suitable liquid in order to produce the gases.</p>
            <p space="8">As the liquid is electrolyzed, the component gases will be stored in its internal tanks - should either tank fill completely, the Separator will turn off.</p>
            <p space="8">If you are only using a single gas, selecting "dumping" or "dumping excess" for the unused gas will vent it to the environment, preventing that internal tank from filling completely and stopping processing.</p>
            <p space="8">Please note that while the Electrolytic Separator does take Energy Upgrades, they don't affect the machine's energy <span underline="true">efficiency</span> (no, you can't break thermodynamics).</p>
            <p space="8">Burning the Hydrogen from Water in the Gas Burning Generator will produce the exact same amount of energy used to Electrolyse the Water. To achieve energy gain, Ethylene must be used.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="energized_smelter">
            <page_title><title>Energized Smelter</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:energized_smelter"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">A furnace that runs off of energy.</p>
            <p space="8">Processes all furnace recipes, unless your modpack has configured exceptions</p>
        </section>
        <section id="energy_cube">
            <page_title><title>Energy Cube</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:basic_energy_cube"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8" align="center">
                <stack item="mekanism:basic_energy_cube" count="1" />
                <stack item="mekanism:advanced_energy_cube" count="1" />
                <stack item="mekanism:elite_energy_cube" count="1" />
                <stack item="mekanism:ultimate_energy_cube" count="1" />
            </p>
            <p space="8">An advanced device for storing and distributing energy.</p>
            <p space="8">Each side can be configured as input or output - make sure you don't create loops!</p>
            <p space="8">In the GUI, items can be charged or drained of power.</p>
            <p space="8">Increasing the tier of Energy Cube increases the total capacity and maximum transfer rate</p>
        </section>
        <section id="enrichment_chamber">
            <page_title><title>Enrichment Chamber</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:enrichment_chamber"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">This machine uses energy to extract dusts out of certain blocks and ores, making it essential to producing different kinds of tools. Not to be mistaken with the Crusher, this machine is the pulverizer equivalent in other mods.</p>
            <p space="8">It can also perform other enriching tasks, such as turning Coal, Charcoal, Redstone, and Obsidian (dust) into their compressed variants.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="factories">
            <page_title><title>Factories</title></page_title>
            <p space="8">Factories are advanced forms of the basic machines aimed to assist in large scale resource processing. They come in 4 tiers: Basic, Advanced, Elite, and Ultimate.</p>
            <p space="8">Factories can perform multiple processes simultaneously, and can also auto-balance the inputs among the available process slots (toggled by the Auto Sort option). Power usage increases for each simultaneous operation.</p>
            <!-- TODO link factory installers -->
            <p space="8">A machine or factory can be upgraded in a crafting grid or with a Factory Installer. Note that it is not possible to skip a tier or otherwise combine Installers to fully upgrade a machine.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="fluidic_plenisher">
            <page_title><title>Fluidic Plenisher</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:fluidic_plenisher"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">The Fluidic Plenisher is the exact opposite of the Electric Pump. Instead of pumping fluids out of an area, the Fluidic Plenisher "floods" an area below it until all available open blocks are filled.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="fluid_tank">
            <page_title><title>Fluid Tanks</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:basic_fluid_tank"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8" align="center">
                <stack item="mekanism:basic_fluid_tank" count="1" />
                <stack item="mekanism:advanced_fluid_tank" count="1" />
                <stack item="mekanism:elite_fluid_tank" count="1" />
                <stack item="mekanism:ultimate_fluid_tank" count="1" />
            </p>
            <p space="8">Fluid Tanks are storage blocks to store fluids. The amount of fluid (mB) a fluid tank can store is based on its tier. It will retain its contents when broken.</p>
            <p space="8">The tanks can fill or empty an item via the GUI. An item containing fluid will be drained (if possible), and an empty one will be filler.</p>
            <title>Bucket Mode</title>
            <p space="8">You can hold the sneak key and scroll to change Bucket Mode. If bucket mode is On, the fluid tank will act like a bucket, being able to physically place fluid (sneak right click) and scoop up fluid (right click).</p>
            <p space="8">However, by setting it to On, it also removes the ability to place the fluid tank. Bucket mode must be set to Off in order to place the fluid tank.</p>
            <title>Automation</title>
            <p space="8">Fluid pipes, such as the Mechanical Pipe, can be attached to any face to insert or extract fluid. Given the tank is not a full block, they will look best on the top or bottom faces</p>
            <p space="8">By sneak right-clicking a tank with a Configurator set to any Configurate mode, auto-output can be toggled. When enabled, fluid will automatically be ejected on the bottom face of the tank, assuming that the destination can accept the fluid. A tank will glow when auto-output is enabled.</p>
            <title>Fluid towers</title>
            <p space="8">Tanks stacked vertically will automatically push fluid upwards when full as if it were part of the same tank. To push fluid downwards in the stack, auto-output must be turned on</p>
        </section>
        <section id="formulaic_assemblicator">
            <page_title><title>Formulaic Assemblicator</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:formulaic_assemblicator"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">A machine that uses energy to rapidly craft items and blocks from Crafting Formulas.</p>
            <p space="8">With a crafting formula installed, the recipe is fixed. Can be used as a normal Crafting Table.</p>
            <p space="8">1. Place a Crafting Formula in the Crafting Formula Slot of the Formulaic Assemblicator.</p>
            <p space="8">2. Place the items for the recipe you wish to craft in the Crafting Grid, and then click the Encode Formula Button.</p>
            <p space="8">3. The Formula is now ready for use with the Formulaic Assemblicator.</p>
            <title>Buttons</title>
            <p space="4" bold="true">Encode Formula</p>
            <p space="8">Encodes the current crafting grid recipe to the Crafting Formula in the Formula slot (requires blank Formula).</p>
            <p space="8">To clear a formula, hold it in your hand and sneak-right click.</p>
            <p space="4" bold="true">Stock Control</p>
            <p space="8">Reserves a slot for each required item in the Formula, preventing the inventory from becoming too full of other items.</p>
            <p space="4" bold="true">Fill/Empty Grid</p>
            <p space="8">When a Crafting Formula is installed, fills the crafting grid from the internal inventory. Without a Formula, empties the crafting grid to the internal inventory.</p>
            <p space="4" bold="true">Craft Single Item</p>
            <p space="8">Just what it sounds like. Does not require power.</p>
            <p space="4" bold="true">Craft Available Items</p>
            <p space="8">Crafts as many items as possible from the available items in the inventory. Does not require power.</p>
            <p space="4" bold="true">Auto Mode</p>
            <p space="8">Continuously craft the Formula when items are available. Requires power.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="fuelwood_heater">
            <page_title><title>Fuelwood Heater</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:fuelwood_heater"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">A machine that is capable of producing heat energy by burning combustible items.</p>
            <p space="8">Heat can be transmitted from any side.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="isotopic_centrifuge">
            <page_title><title>Isotopic Centrifuge</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:isotopic_centrifuge"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">The Isotopic Centrifuge is used with a Fission Reactor, either processing Uranium Hexafluoride into Fissile Fuel, OR processing Nuclear Waste into Plutonium.</p>
            <p space="8">It intakes gas from the bottom only and outputs from the front port only.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="logistical_sorter">
            <page_title><title>Logistical Sorter</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:logistical_sorter"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">Filter which items you are sending and where they go.</p>
            <p space="8">Connect the larger side to a block with an inventory and the smaller side with a Logistical Transporter network.</p>
            <p space="8">Add colours to Logistical Transporter outputs with the Configurator to control where items are routed to.</p>
            <title>Main options</title>
            <p space="4" bold="true">Single</p>
            <p space="8">Sends a single item instead of a whole stack each time (overrides min and max set in ItemStack filters)</p>
            <p space="4" bold="true">RR (Round Robin)</p>
            <p space="8">Turning on this mode will make the Sorter cycle through available destinations when sending items. When this option is off, items will be sent to the closest available inventory.</p>
            <p space="4" bold="true">Auto ( Auto-Eject )</p>
            <p space="8">Turning on auto-eject will cause all items to be pumped out. Turning off auto-eject will cause only items that match a filter to be pumped.</p>
            <p space="4" bold="true">Default</p>
            <p space="8">The default color tag for items. Filtered items that do not have a color tag set will use the default color tag. Left and right click will cycle forwards and backwards through the color list</p>
            <p space="4" bold="true">Item Filters</p>
            <p space="8">Any item filters you create will appear in the main section of the GUI. You can edit existing filters by clicking them.</p>
            <p space="4" bold="true">New Filter</p>
            <p space="8">Click to create a new item filter.</p>

            <title>Common Filter Configuration</title>
            <p space="4" bold="true">Color (bottom left slot)</p>
            <p space="8">Assign a specific color to this filter. Left and right click will cycle forwards and backwards through the color list.</p>
            <p space="4" bold="true">Allow Default</p>
            <p space="8">When turned on, the filtered item will use the default color tag instead if no inventory is available. Note that 'Auto-Eject' must be turned on for this to work</p>
            <p space="4" bold="true">Size Mode, Min, &amp; Max</p>
            <p space="8">Size mode will force the sorter to send a precise amount of items</p>
            <p space="4" bold="true">Fuzzy Mode</p>
            <p space="8">The sorter will ignore if a tool, weapon or armor is damaged or not.</p>

            <title>Filter Types</title>
            <p space="4" bold="true">ItemStack (Item)</p>
            <p space="8">Matches specific Item types. Click an item into the top-left slot.</p>
            <p space="4" bold="true">Tag</p>
            <p space="8">Uses the tag system to search for Items in a group. You can use a Dictionary to find these.</p>
            <p space="8">Type a name and click the green tick to check your entry.</p>
            <p space="4">Some examples</p>
            <p space="8"><span italics="true">forge:ores</span> - All ores</p>
            <p space="8"><span italics="true">forge:ores/iron</span> - All Iron ore variants</p>
            <p space="8"><span italics="true">forge:sand</span> - Sand</p>
            <p space="8"><span italics="true">minecraft:logs</span> - Wood Logs</p>
            <p space="8"><span italics="true">minecraft:seeds</span> - Seeds</p>
            <p space="4" bold="true">Mod ID</p>
            <p space="8">Searches for any item from a specific mod. Mod IDs are all lowercase and can often be found online on wikis.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="metallurgic_infuser">
            <page_title><title>Metallurgic Infuser</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:metallurgic_infuser"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">A machine used to infuse various materials into (generally) metals to create metal alloys and other compounds.</p>
            <p space="8">Contains an Infusion Material slot and an Input slot.</p>
            <p space="8">Generally you will want a separate one for each infusion type, though the infusion tank can be Dumped to clear it for another type.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="modification_station">
            <page_title><title>Modification Station</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:modification_station"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">The Modification Station is used for applying modular upgrades to the Meka-Suit and the Meka-Tool in exchange for energy.</p>
            <p space="8">A part of the Meka-Suit or the Meka-Tool is inserted into the station along with the upgrade, resulting in the upgrade being applied (if compatible).</p>
            <p space="8">It functions similarly to an Anvil or a Power Armor Tinker Table from the Modular Powersuits mod.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="nutritional_liquifier">
            <page_title><title>Nutritional Liquifier</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:nutritional_liquifier"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">The Nutritional Liquifier turns consumable food items into Nutritional Paste.</p>
            <p space="8">It can hold a total of 10000mB of paste before it is full and halts production.</p>
            <p space="8">The nutritional paste is used by the MekaSuit Helmet and the Canteen for feeding the player without having to carry physical individual food items in their inventory.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="oredictionificator">
            <page_title><title>Oredictionificator</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:oredictionificator"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">Named after the old Ore Dictionary feature, this block allows conversion between equivalent items/block between mods.</p>
            <p space="8">For example, Mekanism Tin Ore to another mod's Tin Ore.</p>
            <p space="8">Generally this process shouldn't be necessary, but sometimes a specific variant is required (or desired).</p>
            <p space="8">Open the GUI to configure which items/blocks to output, then either place the items in the slot or use pipes.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="osmium_compressor">
            <page_title><title>Osmium Compressor</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:osmium_compressor"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">Infuses Liquid Osmium into various materials to make things such as Refined Glowstone and Refined Obsidian.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="painting_machine">
            <page_title><title>Painting Machine</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:painting_machine"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">A machine used to color blocks and items via a careful application of a stored pigment.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="personal_barrel">
            <page_title><title>Personal Barrel</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:personal_barrel"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">A barrel which can be security controlled by Mekanism's security system.</p>
            <p space="8">It can be accessed by the Use action, or placed as a block with the sneak-use action.</p>
            <p space="8">The first use will assign ownership.</p>
            <p space="8">Note that it must be set to Public security to use item pipes (including Logistical Transporters) with it.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="personal_chest">
            <page_title><title>Personal Chest</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:personal_chest"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">A chest which can be security controlled by Mekanism's security system.</p>
            <p space="8">It can be accessed by the Use action, or placed as a block with the sneak-use action.</p>
            <p space="8">The first use will assign ownership.</p>
            <p space="8">Note that it must be set to Public security to use item pipes (including Logistical Transporters) with it.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="pigment_extractor">
            <page_title><title>Pigment Extractor</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:pigment_extractor"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">A machine used to extract pigments from blocks and items.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="pigment_mixer">
            <page_title><title>Pigment Mixer</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:pigment_mixer"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">A sturdy machine capable of mixing two pigments together to produce a new pigment.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="precision_sawmill">
            <page_title><title>Precision Sawmill</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:precision_sawmill"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">The Precision Sawmill is used for reclaiming wood from wooden items and turning logs into planks with a better yield than a crafting table.</p>
            <p space="8">Also makes sawdust for use in making Cardboard Box.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="pressurized_reaction_chamber">
            <page_title><title>Pressurized Reaction Chamber</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:pressurized_reaction_chamber"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">The Pressurized Reaction Chamber (PRC) is used primarily to create Substrate (to create HDPE Pellets), HDPE Pellets (to create HDPE Sheets), and Ethylene (an efficient source of fuel used in the Gas-Burning Generator).</p>
            <p space="8">It has a variable speed and energy usage dependent on the materials/gasses it is creating.</p>
            <p space="8">The PRC can accept a Liquid input, a Gas input and an Item input while outputting an Item and a Liquid. You may need 5 sides available for automation!</p>
        </section>
        <section id="purification_chamber">
            <page_title><title>Purification Chamber</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:purification_chamber"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">The Purification Chamber uses oxygen to refine Ores and shards into clumps.</p>
            <p space="8">The oxygen can be provided externally as gas, internally with an oxygen filled Gas Tank or flint.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="resistive_heater">
            <page_title><title>Resistive Heater</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:resistive_heater"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">A condensed, coiled resistor capable of converting electrical energy directly into heat energy.</p>
            <p space="8">Set the desired energy usage in the GUI, and heat will be produced.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="robit">
            <page_title><title>Robit</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:robit"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">Robit is Mekanism's mechanical companion. He can act as a crafting grid, a furnace, an anvil, a chest, or simply a cute little buddy.</p>
            <p space="8">To bring your Robit into the world, they must be placed onto a powered Chargepad. This will serve as their home location (which they can teleport to) as well as providing them a way to recharge their battery.</p>
            <p space="8">Various options can be toggled in your Robit's GUI - Robit's name, follow mode, pickup dropped items, teleport home (Robit only, you cannot come for a ride), change appearance.</p>
            <p space="8">Robit also has a small inventory, a 9x9 crafting grid, a small smelter, and an Anvil.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="rotary_condensentrator">
            <page_title><title>Rotary Condensentrator</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:rotary_condensentrator"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">The Rotary Condensentrator (pronounced "con-DEN-sen-tray-tor") is used for converting substances between liquid and gaseous forms at a rate of 1:1.</p>
            <p space="8">It has two modes: Decondensentrating, which turns Liquids into Gases, and Condensentrating, which turns Gases into Liquids. Press the T button in the GUI to switch between modes.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="seismic_vibrator">
            <page_title><title>Seismic Vibrator</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:seismic_vibrator"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">The Seismic Vibrator shakes the ground, which allows for the Seismic Reader to function.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="solar_neutron_activator">
            <page_title><title>Solar Neutron Activator</title></page_title>
            <recipe type="crafting">
                <recipe.result>
                    <stack item="mekanism:solar_neutron_activator"/>
                </recipe.result>
            </recipe>
            <space height="3"/>
            <p space="8">The Solar Neutron Activator is a machine that directs the neutron radiation of the sun into its internal reservoir, allowing for the slow creation of various isotopes.</p>
            <p space="8">The input is at the bottom, the output is at the front. It does not need energy except for direct sunlight. There must be no blocks between it and the sky.</p>
        </section>
    </chapter>
    <chapter id="gear">

    </chapter>
    <chapter id="items">

    </chapter>
</book>
